loveme.com 2017-06-28

# Privacy Policy

This **Privacy Policy** may be modified from time to time; the date of the most recent revision will appear on this page, so check back often. Continued access to the site by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy. 

It is our goal to bring you information that is tailored to your individual needs and, at the same time, protect your privacy. The following is a summary of the various ways we treat the information you provide us while using our site. 

**THE TYPE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED**

We generally collect personally identifying information with your specific knowledge and consent. For instance, when you enter a sweepstakes or contest, complete a survey, make a purchase, subscribe to our newsletters, or register for any portion of our services, you are asked to provide information, such as your e-mail address, name or phone number. Optional information such as your age or gender may also be requested.

**USE OF INFORMATION PROVIDED BY YOU**

We use this information to provide you with the service you have requested. For example, if you subscribe to our newsletters, we may use your e-mail address to send you a confirmation notice; if you subscribe to our catalog, we may use your address to send you our catalog. Similarly, if you enter an online sweepstakes, we will use this information to notify you if you are a winner. We may also use the information to communicate with you about new features, products or services, or to improve the services that we offer by tailoring them to your needs. 

We do not sell our users' email addresses or mailing addresses. If you do not wish to receive communications from us, simply follow the unsubscribe instructions contained with the e-mail. If you are registered on any part of the site you may also change or update your member preferences or information with any section of the site where you have signed up, registered or created any type of account. 

We also allow access to our database by third parties that provide us with services, such as technical maintenance, but only for the purpose of and to the extent necessary to provide those services. While we will seek to require such third parties to follow appropriate privacy policies and will not authorize them to use this information except for the express purpose for which it is provided, we do not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of third parties. There may also be occasion when we are legally required to provide access to our database in order to cooperate with police investigations or other legal proceedings. In those instances, the information is provided only for that purpose. 

**COOKIES**

You may have read about "cookies," nuggets of information that are placed by a Web site in a storage place on your own computer. We use cookies to personalize your usage, to track usage patterns on the site, and to record registration and personalization information. For example, if you register on any part of the site you can opt to save your user name and password on your computer. We can provide this convenience by placing a cookie on your computer. 

If you don't want cookies, your Web browser likely includes an option that allows you to not accept them. However, if you set your browser to refuse cookies, some portions of the site may not function properly. 

While your individual information is protected as outlined above, we reserve the right to use aggregated anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners. 

**IP ADDRESS**

Your Internet Protocol ("IP") address is usually associated with the place from which you enter the Internet, like your Internet Service Provider, your company or your university. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, gather broad demographic information, and administer our Web site. 

**KIDS AND PARENTS**

The site is not intended for use by children. 

If you have other concerns or questions about any aspect of this policy, you may also e-mail our Privacy Policy Coordinator. We welcome your feedback. You can also send us regular mail at the following address: 

A Foreign Affair   
CO / Privacy Policy Coordinator  
7320 N Dreamy Draw Drive  
Phoenix AZ 85020

_Page last updated March 16, 2017_

---  

THIS PROGRAM IS THE SOLE PROPERTY OF **A FOREIGN AFFAIR** AND MAY NOT BE COPIED   
IN ANY WAY OR FORM WITHOUT EXPRESS PERMISSION FROM **A FOREIGN AFFAIR**. 

© COPYRIGHT 1996-2017 - ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.
